<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Report Name="WeeklyHighlightsReport" xmlns="WeeklyHighlightsReport"><Tablix1><Details_Collection><Details Textbox1="This summary is based on reports from exporters for the period March 20-26, 2026.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Wheat: Net sales of 23,500 metric tons (MT) for 2025/2026--a marketing-year low--were down 51 percent from the previous week and 33 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for Nigeria (47,000 MT, including decreases of 3,000 MT), Tanzania (47,000 MT), the Dominican Republic (14,400 MT), Japan (9,400 MT, including decreases of 100 MT), and Belize (6,800 MT), were offset by reductions for unknown destinations (60,100 MT), Mexico (56,200 MT), and Indonesia (700 MT). Net sales of 272,800 MT for 2026/2027 were reported for Mexico (172,200 MT), South Korea (65,000 MT), Honduras (15,600 MT), Jamaica (15,000 MT), and Japan (5,000 MT). Exports of 340,900 MT were down 11 percent from the previous week and 12 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Japan (107,600 MT), Mexico (96,700 MT), the Philippines (58,800 MT), Nigeria (47,000 MT), and Haiti (13,000 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Corn: Net sales of 1,149,400 MT for 2025/2026 were down 8 percent from the previous week and 20 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for Mexico (170,700 MT, including decreases of 38,300 MT), Japan (168,800 MT, including 161,200 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 5,700 MT), Taiwan (150,900 MT, including 65,000 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 100 MT), Colombia (120,800 MT, including 91,000 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 1,200 MT), and Venezuela (78,800 MT, including decreases of 1,000 MT), were offset by reductions for Hong Kong (100 MT). Total net sales of 102,600 MT for 2026/2027 were for Mexico. Exports of 1,994,700 MT were up 19 percent from the previous week and 17 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Mexico (448,100 MT), Japan (362,400 MT), South Korea (282,400 MT), Colombia (230,400 MT), and Egypt (161,300 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Barley: No net sales for 2025/2026 were reported for the week. Exports of 1,100 MT were to Canada (600 MT) and Japan (500 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Sorghum: Net sales of 112,000 MT for 2025/2026 were up noticeably from the previous week and from the prior 4-week average. Increases reported for China (178,000 MT, including 126,000 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 5,000 MT), were offset by reductions for unknown destinations (66,000 MT). Exports of 183,300 MT were down 5 percent from the previous week and 18 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destination was to China.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Rice: Net sales of 84,800 MT for 2025/2026 were up noticeably from the previous week and up 96 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for Mexico (62,300 MT, including decreases of 100 MT), unknown destinations (20,000 MT), Nicaragua (10,100 MT), Haiti (9,800 MT, including decreases of 13,000 MT), and South Korea (5,600 MT), were offset by reductions for Colombia (26,800 MT) and Saudi Arabia (300 MT). Total net sales of 5,600 MT for 2026/2027 were for South Korea. Exports of 55,200 MT were up noticeably from the previous week and up 47 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Honduras (15,400 MT), Haiti (13,600 MT), Japan (13,600 MT), South Korea (3,300 MT), and Mexico (2,300 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Soybeans: Net sales of 353,300 MT for 2025/2026 were down 49 percent from the previous week and 18 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for China (141,000 MT, including 134,000 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 500 MT), Bangladesh (91,400 MT), Mexico (83,600 MT, including decreases of 1,400 MT), Indonesia (55,800 MT, including 34,000 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 100 MT), and Egypt (53,200 MT, including 55,000 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 1,800 MT), were offset by reductions for unknown destinations (159,800 MT), Venezuela (6,000 MT), and Costa Rica (200 MT). Exports of 681,900 MT were down 49 percent from the previous week and 36 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to China (341,000 MT), Indonesia (77,300 MT), Egypt (53,200 MT), Japan (51,100 MT), and Mexico (43,800 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Soybean Cake and Meal: Net sales of 377,200 MT for 2025/2026 were down 40 percent from the previous week, but up 19 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for unknown destinations (112,600 MT), the Philippines (54,700 MT), Ecuador (42,000 MT), Mexico (40,200 MT, including decreases of 9,800 MT), and Colombia (33,400 MT, including decreases of 700 MT), were offset by reductions for El Salvador (6,600 MT), Belgium (1,100 MT), Japan (700 MT), Hong Kong (300 MT), and Burma (100 MT). Total net sales of 200 MT for 2026/2027 were for Canada. Exports of 401,400 MT were up 6 percent from the previous week and 15 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to the Philippines (94,600 MT), Mexico (66,400 MT), Poland (66,000 MT), Colombia (52,500 MT), and Ecuador (36,700 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Optional Origin Sales: For 2025/2026, decreases of 2,000 MT were for Ecuador. The current outstanding balance of 21,800 MT, all Ecuador. For 2026/2027, new optional origin sales of 2,000 MT were for Ecuador. The current outstanding balance of 2,000 MT, all Ecuador.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Soybean Oil: Net sales of 1,100 MT for 2025/2026 were up 53 percent from the previous week, but down 58 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases reported for Canada (3,100 MT, including decreases of 700 MT), were offset by reductions for Guatemala (2,000 MT). Exports of 6,500 MT were down 76 percent from the previous week and 69 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Venezuela (4,100 MT), Mexico (1,500 MT), and the Dominican Republic (700 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Cotton: Net sales of Upland totaling 371,500 RB for 2025/2026 were up noticeably from the previous week and up 94 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for Vietnam (170,500 RB, including 3,300 RB switched from China and decreases of 4,900 RB), Turkey (59,400 RB, including decreases of 100 RB), China (55,000 RB, including decreases of 100 RB), Pakistan (45,600 RB), and Bangladesh (9,200 RB), were offset by reductions for Indonesia (1,500 RB) and Honduras (300 RB). Net sales of 117,300 RB for 2026/2027 were primarily for Turkey (39,600 RB), Mexico (37,000 RB), Japan (32,100 RB), Thailand (3,800 RB), and Vietnam (3,500 RB). Exports of 356,700 RB were down 11 percent from the previous week, but up 8 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Vietnam (104,100 RB), Pakistan (38,600 RB), Bangladesh (36,100 RB), Turkey (32,000 RB), and India (28,600 RB). Net sales of Pima totaling 15,500 RB for 2025/2026 were down 50 percent from the previous week, but up 16 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases were primarily for China (8,500 RB), India (3,500 RB), Peru (2,000 RB), Vietnam (500 RB), and Turkey (300 RB). Exports of 7,600 RB were down 3 percent from the previous week and 30 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to India (3,200 RB), Pakistan (1,400 RB), Egypt (1,300 RB), China (500 RB), and Peru (300 RB).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Exports for Own Account: For 2025/2026, new exports for own account totaling 1,600 RB were to Vietnam (1,200 RB) and Bangladesh (400 RB). Exports for own account totaling 700 MT to Vietnam were applied to new or outstanding sales. The current exports for own account outstanding balance of 8,800 RB were to India (5,300 RB), Vietnam (2,600 RB), Turkey (500 RB), and Bangladesh (400 RB).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Hides and Skins: Net sales of 283,700 pieces for 2026 were primarily for China (164,300 whole cattle hides, including decreases of 4,200 pieces), Mexico (55,600 whole cattle hides, including decreases of 500 pieces), Brazil (32,200 whole cattle hides), South Korea (27,100 whole cattle hides, including decreases of 1,700 pieces), and Thailand (16,000 whole cattle hides, including decreases of 200 pieces), were offset by reductions for Turkey (25,200 pieces) and Italy (700 pieces). Exports of 294,700 whole cattle hides were primarily to China (169,400 pieces), Mexico (52,600 pieces), South Korea (38,500 pieces), Thailand (17,900 pieces), and Brazil (11,500 pieces).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Net sales of 246,800 wet blues for 2026 were primarily for Vietnam (90,600 unsplit), Hong Kong (59,900 unsplit, including decreases of 100 unsplit), Thailand (37,300 unsplit), Italy (23,000 unsplit), and Guyana (17,300 unsplit). Net sales of 23,800 wet blues for 2027 were reported for Hong Kong (18,000 unsplit) and Guyana (5,800 unsplit). Total net sales of 3,100 other excluding wet blues were for Turkey. Exports of 167,100 wet blues were primarily to Vietnam (84,600 unsplit), Italy (31,700 unsplit), Hong Kong (26,300 unsplit), China (11,000 unsplit), and Brazil (6,500 unsplit). Exports of 5,400 other excluding wet blues were to Turkey (4,600 pounds) and China (800 pounds). Net sales of 437,400 splits reported for China (438,000 pounds), were offset by reductions for Taiwan (600 pounds). Exports of 127,200 splits were to Taiwan (83,400 pounds) and China (43,800 pounds).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Beef: Net sales of 11,900 MT for 2026 were up 12 percent from the previous week, but down 6 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for South Korea (3,800 MT, including decreases of 600 MT), Japan (3,100 MT, including decreases of 1,700 MT), Mexico (1,300 MT), Taiwan (1,200 MT, including decreases of 300 MT), and Hong Kong (800 MT, including decreases of 300 MT), were offset by reductions for the Philippines (100 MT). Exports of 13,600 MT were down 5 percent from the previous week, but unchanged from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to South Korea (4,500 MT), Japan (2,900 MT), Mexico (1,500 MT), Taiwan (1,100 MT), and Hong Kong (1,100 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Export Adjustments: Accumulated exports of beef to the Netherlands were adjusted down 72 MT for week ending March 19. This shipment was reported in error.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Pork: Net sales of 53,000 MT for 2026 were up 32 percent from the previous week and 65 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases were primarily for Mexico (39,100 MT, including decreases of 400 MT), Japan (3,300 MT, including decreases of 400 MT), Colombia (2,000 MT, including decreases of 300 MT), South Korea (1,800 MT, including decreases of 100 MT), and the Dominican Republic (1,600 MT). Exports of 39,800 MT were up 2 percent from the previous week and 5 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Mexico (17,500 MT), Japan (5,200 MT), South Korea (4,400 MT), China (3,400 MT), and Colombia (2,100 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;April 2, 2026                                       1                  FOREIGN AGRICULTURAL SERVICE/USDA&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;SUMMARY OF EXPORT TRANSACTIONS&#xD;&#xA;Reported Under the Daily Reporting System&#xD;&#xA;For Period Ending March 26, 2026&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Commodity Destination                 Quantity (MT) Marketing&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Soybeans   Unknown                    105,000 MT 1/   2025/2026&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;1/Export sales.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA; " /></Details_Collection></Tablix1></Report>