<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Report Name="WeeklyHighlightsReport" xmlns="WeeklyHighlightsReport"><Tablix1><Details_Collection><Details Textbox1="This summary is based on reports from exporters for the period March 27-April 2, 2026.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Wheat: Net sales of 163,600 metric tons (MT) for 2025/2026 were up noticeably from the previous week, but down 39 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for Venezuela (52,500 MT, including 49,000 MT switched from unknown destinations), Japan (51,000 MT), Burma (45,000 MT, including 16,800 MT switched from unknown destinations), Malaysia (21,500 MT, including 20,900 MT switched from unknown destinations), and the Dominican Republic (20,200 MT, including decreases of 400 MT), were offset by reductions for unknown destinations (118,300 MT) and Costa Rica (100 MT). Net sales of 90,700 MT for 2026/2027 were primarily for Mexico (33,800 MT), the Philippines (18,000 MT), Japan (14,800 MT), unknown destinations (10,000 MT), and El Salvador (7,100 MT). Exports of 371,200 MT were up 9 percent from the previous week, but down 4 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Mexico (92,300 MT), South Korea (55,000 MT), Venezuela (52,500 MT), the Dominican Republic (28,200 MT), and Honduras (27,100 MT).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Corn: Net sales of 1,361,300 MT for 2025/2026 were up 18 percent from the previous week and 8 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for Japan (632,400 MT, including 224,700 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 48,100 MT), Mexico (202,500 MT, including 60,000 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 15,300 MT), Colombia (177,500 MT, including 98,900 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 5,300 MT), Portugal (109,700 MT, including 65,000 MT switched from unknown destinations), and Ireland (80,000 MT, including 81,900 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 1,900 MT), were offset by reductions primarily for unknown destinations (322,900 MT). Total net sales of 11,400 MT for 2026/2027 were for Mexico. Exports of 1,829,900 MT were down 8 percent from the previous week, but up 3 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Mexico (457,500 MT), Japan (433,600 MT), Colombia (279,100 MT), South Korea (134,400 MT), and Ireland (80,000 MT).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Barley: No net sales for 2025/2026 were reported for the week. Total net sales of 3,100 MT for 2026/2027 were for Canada. Exports of 1,300 MT were to Canada.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Sorghum: Total net sales of 113,500 MT for 2025/2026 were up 1 percent from the previous week and 99 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases were for China. Exports of 62,800 MT were down 66 percent from the previous week and 68 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destination was China.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Rice: Net sales of 4,800 MT for 2025/2026 were down 94 percent from the previous week and 92 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for unknown destinations (10,500 MT), Honduras (5,200 MT), Canada (5,100 MT, including decreases of 200 MT), Mexico (2,100 MT, including decreases of 100 MT), and Saudi Arabia (1,500 MT), were offset by reductions for Japan (12,800 MT), Haiti (7,100 MT), Jordan (200 MT), and Nicaragua (100 MT). Total net sales of 300 MT for 2026/2027 were for Taiwan. Exports of 17,300 MT were down 69 percent from the previous week and 61 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Haiti (7,500 MT), Mexico (2,200 MT), Taiwan (2,100 MT), Canada (2,100 MT), and Japan (900 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Soybeans: Net sales of 295,400 MT for 2025/2026 were down 16 percent from the previous week and 34 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for China (124,700 MT, including 121,000 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 3,800 MT), Japan (104,800 MT, including 20,200 MT switched from unknown destinations and decreases of 200 MT), Egypt (47,000 MT), Mexico (27,500 MT, including decreases of 200 MT), and Indonesia (17,100 MT, including decreases of 100 MT), were offset by reductions for unknown destinations (77,400 MT) and Barbados (400 MT). Exports of 636,000 MT were down 7 percent from the previous week and 35 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to China (430,700 MT), Mexico (65,400 MT), Indonesia (34,400 MT), Japan (33,900 MT), and Colombia (16,000 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Soybean Cake and Meal: Net sales of 363,600 MT for 2025/2026 were down 4 percent from the previous week, but up 14 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for the Philippines (153,300 MT, including 45,000 MT switched from unknown destinations), Mexico (66,100 MT, including decreases of 100 MT), the Dominican Republic (50,900 MT), Honduras (14,600 MT, including 4,800 MT switched from El Salvador and decreases of 11,500 MT), and Colombia (13,500 MT, including 6,000 MT switched from Ecuador, 6,000 MT switched from unknown destinations, and decreases of 7,100 MT), were offset by reductions for Japan (1,800 MT). Total net sales of 4,000 MT for 2026/2027 were for Canada. Exports of 458,800 MT were up 14 percent from the previous week and 19 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to the Philippines (156,500 MT), Mexico (72,700 MT), Colombia (49,200 MT), Guatemala (31,400 MT), and Nicaragua (23,300 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Soybean Oil: Net sales reductions of 1,600 MT for 2025/2026 were down noticeably from the previous week and from the prior 4-week average. Increases reported for Mexico (900 MT, including decreases of 200 MT), were more than offset by reductions for Colombia (2,400 MT) and Canada (100 MT). Exports of 1,500 MT--a marketing-year low--were down 78 percent from the previous week and 91 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were to Mexico (1,100 MT) and Canada (400 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Cotton: Net sales of Upland totaling 319,600 RB for 2025/2026 were down 14 percent from the previous week, but up 25 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for Vietnam (132,500 RB, including decreases of 900 RB), Turkey (67,800 RB), Pakistan (36,000 RB), India (24,200 RB, including 400 RB switched from Sri Lanka), and Bangladesh (18,700 RB, including decreases of 200 RB), were offset by reductions for Switzerland (3,700 RB), Nicaragua (1,300 RB), and Sri Lanka (400 RB). Net sales of 14,100 RB for 2026/2027 primarily for Costa Rica (13,200 RB), Indonesia (9,300 RB), South Korea (6,500 RB), Bangladesh (5,300 RB), and Portugal (3,500 RB), were offset by reductions for Japan (25,000 RB). Exports of 342,700 RB were down 4 percent from the previous week and 2 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Vietnam (126,200 RB), China (39,000 RB), India (37,100 RB), Pakistan (32,900 RB), and Bangladesh (32,100 RB). Net sales of Pima totaling 6,500 RB for 2025/2026 were down 58 percent from the previous week and from the prior 4-week average. Increases were primarily for China (2,900 RB, including decreases of 100 RB), India (1,400 RB), Thailand (900 RB), Bangladesh (500 RB), and Japan (400 RB). Exports of 10,600 RB were up 40 percent from the previous week and 10 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to India (4,300 RB), Pakistan (2,800 RB), Costa Rica (1,300 RB), Peru (1,200 RB), and Bangladesh (500 RB).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Exports for Own Account: For 2025/2026, exports for own account totaling 4,500 MT to India were applied to new or outstanding sales. &#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Hides and Skins: Net sales of 269,500 pieces for 2026 primarily for China (173,200 whole cattle hides, including decreases of 6,200 pieces), Mexico (51,600 whole cattle hides, including decreases of 500 pieces), Thailand (30,900 whole cattle hides, including decreases of 100 pieces), Italy (11,200 whole cattle hides), and Turkey (2,200 whole cattle hides), were offset by reductions for Brazil (100 pieces) and India (100 pieces). Exports of 271,200 whole cattle hides were primarily to China (177,700 pieces), Mexico (29,600 pieces), South Korea (19,200 pieces), Brazil (19,000 pieces), and Thailand (15,700 pieces).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Net sales of 154,100 wet blues for 2026 were primarily for Thailand (52,200 unsplit), China (33,600 unsplit), Vietnam (25,600 unsplit, including decreases of 300 unsplit), Italy (20,800 unsplit), and Brazil (11,100 unsplit). Total net sales of 9,200 other excluding wet blues were for Turkey, including decreases of 1,500 pounds. Exports of 141,700 wet blues were primarily to Vietnam (59,300 unsplit), Italy (38,600 unsplit), China (12,800 unsplit), Brazil (12,600 unsplit), and Hong Kong (9,600 unsplit). No exports of other excluding wet blues were reported for the week. No net sales or exports of splits were reported for the week.&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Beef: Net sales of 17,400 MT for 2026 were up 47 percent from the previous week and 36 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases were primarily for South Korea (6,100 MT, including decreases of 400 MT), Japan (6,100 MT, including decreases of 100 MT), Mexico (1,100 MT), Hong Kong (900 MT, including decreases of 100 MT), and Taiwan (900 MT, including decreases of 300 MT). Exports of 13,300 MT were down 2 percent from the previous week, but up 1 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to South Korea (4,600 MT), Japan (3,800 MT), Mexico (1,400 MT), Hong Kong (1,100 MT), and Taiwan (900 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Pork: Net sales of 31,300 MT for 2026 were down 41 percent from the previous week and 14 percent from the prior 4-week average. Increases primarily for Mexico (14,700 MT), Japan (3,700 MT, including decreases of 600 MT), South Korea (1,800 MT, including decreases of 400 MT), China (1,500 MT), and Colombia (1,500 MT, including decreases of 200 MT), were offset by reductions for Denmark (200 MT). Exports of 35,100 MT were down 12 percent from the previous week and 8 percent from the prior 4-week average. The destinations were primarily to Mexico (14,400 MT), Japan (4,900 MT), South Korea (4,500 MT), China (3,600 MT), and Canada (1,800 MT).&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;April 9, 2026                                       1                  FOREIGN AGRICULTURAL SERVICE/USDA&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;SUMMARY OF EXPORT TRANSACTIONS&#xD;&#xA;Reported Under the Daily Reporting System&#xD;&#xA;For Period Ending April 2, 2026&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Commodity Destination                 Quantity (MT) Marketing&#xD;&#xA; &#xD;&#xA;Corn Unknown                   145,000 MT 1/ 2025/2026&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;1/ Export sales." /></Details_Collection></Tablix1></Report>